ABHIMANYU (MANYU) LAKHOTIA

+1(337)322-4192 \$\text{LakeMonYew@gmail.com}\$ https://portfolio.majorziploc.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/majorziploc/ https://github.com/MajorZiploc

Software Developer with 3+ years of work experience in developing web applications, documenting, stand alone applications, cicd, and databases; along with personal experience in scripting, web scraping, data analytics, and data cleaning.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend React, asp.net mvc, winforms

Backend/Testing/Headless F# Giraffe, google app suite scripts, cypress.io, pandas, webscraper.io, tampermonkey

Languages F#, bash, typescript, javascript, python, sql, powershell, C#, rust, mongodb

DevOps Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, docker, ansible, github actions, vmware

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer \rightarrow Technical Lead - Full time - Team size: 4-10 Acadian Ambulance

Mar 2020 - Present Lafayette, LA

- Introduced automated UI and API testing using Cypress.io
- Heavy improvements to powershell, google app suite scripts (with npm clasp) and documentation practices
- Created interface for interacting/managing over 100 projects using just command runner, bash, and webscraper.io
- Utilize tools like: F#, C#, react, wsl, mssql, just, vim, bash, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, SSIS, and SSRS

Freelance Software Developer - Part time - Team size: 3-6 Cythereal

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021 Lafayette, LA

- Introduced documentation of projects, cicd pipelines, and other processes to remove knowledge silos
- Utilized tools like: python, django, docker, mongodb, react, nodejs, vim, bash, azure, ansible, terraform, packer, and just

Quality Engineer/Consultant - Full time - Team size: 20-25

Feb 2019 - Feb 2020 Lafayette, LA

- Wrote automated UI and API test suites a health insurance website
- Utilized tools like: typescript, protractor, postgresql, mongodb, docker, vscode, and bash

Undergraduate Programming Languages Research Assistant - Part time University Of Louisiana

May 2018 - Dec 2018 Lafayette, LA

Software Developer Intern - Part time - Team size: 4-6

Wetlands Research Center

Jan 2017 - Apr 2018 Lafayette, LA

- Developed a website using asp.net mvc for network monitoring
- Developed a stand alone executable project using java swing for analyzing water levels from large NetCDF files

Sales Associate - Part time - Team size: 4-8

Jul
 2011 - Dec2017 and Mar
 2020 - Present Lafayette, LA

C & M Music Center

- Write MSAccess 95 sql queries to fill in missing gaps of POS software. Ex: Analyze customer purchases
- Write webscraper.io/pandas scripts to scrape/analyze/manage our online Reverb.com item listings
- Write powershell and google app suite scripts for various miscellaneous tasks

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

ison-test-utility A wrapper over lodash to help test api's and much more (Available on npm) (typescript, appveyor)

powershell_scaffolder A module to create new powershell modules (Available on psgallery) (powershell, github actions)

F# projects with contributions FSharpPlus, Acadian.FSharp, Acadian.Dapper.Fs, Acadian.Json.Fs (Available on nuget)

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Economics with Computer Science and Mathematics, University of Louisiana at Lafayette 2016 - 2018 Associates in General Studies Business, South Louisiana Community College

2013 - 2015